http://www.userful.com/company/privacy-policy

IT World Awards - Gold
Userful has been recognized by Network Products Guide as
Most Innovative IT Software
Privacy Policy1. Userful’s Position on PrivacyAt Userful, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit Userful's sites without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself or your organization. There are times, however, when we may need information from you to directly to carry out business operations such as completing your transactions with us, or keeping you informed of our business offerings. It is our responsibility to obtain your consent from you before collecting personal information from you on the Internet.2. What Information Do We Collect?2.1 Personal DataPersonal data is data that can be used to identify you as an individual user. We collect personal data such as your full name, email address, phone number, IP address, domain, and cookie information.2.2 How We Collect Personal DataWe collect this information from you when you browse our website, sign-up for our mailing lists, download our resources, carryout business transactions with us, and from third-party and publicly available sources such as cookies.2.3 Enabling/Disabling CookiesA cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some Userful pages use cookies so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. You can set your browser to notify you each time a cookie is sent, and then choose whether to accept or reject it.3. What Do We Use This Information For?We use this information to improve our business products and services and enhance your overall user experience. Applications of your data to improve our business services may include; marketing/advertising, tailored sales experiences, and product improvement. Userful processes its user’s data in Canada.4. How Is Your Information Disclosed?4.1 UserfulUserful collects and processes data in Canada, and is subject to all applicable Canadian Privacy and Information laws. If you are a user outside of Canada, your national data privacy laws may differ from Canadian law. However, all data collected by Userful is subject to this policy and all applicable laws. If you are an EU User, GDPR protections apply to your data.4.2 Business PartnersUserful works with third-party business partners to develop and deliver its products and services. Your data may be shared with them to improve and personalize business products and services.4.3 Legal Compliance/InvestigationsIf lawfully required by an authorized third-party, Userful may be required to share personal data with a third-party to comply with laws, court orders, and other legal directives. Such authorized third-parties may include; law enforcement, legal counsel, regulatory bodies, and other legally authorized third-parties.5. EU Only: GDPR Compliance5.1 EligibilityFor our EU customers, partners, and other stakeholders, the new GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) legislation has resulted in some changes to our privacy policy and practices. You are protected under GDPR if you are a user accessing our services from the European Union (EU).5.2 Your Rights Under GDPR
Right of Awareness: It is our responsibility to tell you what is happening to your personal data - what we are using it for, why, and where any data processing is taking place. We must have your consent before we process your personal data.
Right of Access: You have the right to request a complete copy of the personal data we’ve collected from you. If you wish to obtain a copy of your data, please contact us.
Right to be Forgotten: If you wish, you can choose to have all the personal data we have collected about you erased and not be used by us or one of our partnered third-parties. If you wish to exercise this right, please contact Userful directly.
Data Portability: In conjunction with your right to access, you can choose to provide your acquired personal data records to other parties. It is your data, and Userful respects your choices over how you choose to manage it.
Prompt Alerts:In the unlikely instance that a security breach occurs which threatens your rights and freedoms, it is our responsibility to notify you within 72 hours of it happening.
6. Protecting Your Data6.1 Internal ProtectionsAll collected personal data is protected under our privacy policy and Canadian law. Although we have established internal safeguards to protect data integrity, we cannot eliminate all risks associated with the storage and use of your data.6.2 External LinksThe Userful site contains links to other websites. Userful is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. For more information on how these third-parties manage their privacy practices, please review their respective privacy policies7. Consent7.1 Explicit ConsentIn specific instances where sensitive personal information is required (such as order processing), we will require your explicit consent to access, use, and store sensitive personal information such as financial information.7.2 Non-Explicit ConsentWith the exception of instances where explicit consent is required, by proceeding to use this site and access its resources, you agree to Userful’s Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions of Use.7.3 Withdrawing ConsentIf you choose to withdraw your consent for Userful to access and use your personal data, we will respect your choice. In accordance to applicable laws, your data may no longer be disclosed to Userful or its affiliates, and all previously stored personal data may be destroyed. You may unsubscribe from all future mailings by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email you receive from us.8. Contact UsPlease contact us with any questions or comments you have about our privacy practices.Last Updated: 01/01/2019
SolutionsVideo Wall SolutionControl RoomsDigital SignageCorporate CommunicationPublic ComputingProductsStandard Professional+ Enterprise Hybrid ProductuClient AppServer ArchitectureThe Visual Networking PlatformUserful for LEDResourcesAboutCompany NewsExecutive TeamBoard of DirectorsCareersBecome A PartnerAwardsEventsContactSchedule DemoGet Pricing
